export const geography = [
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20city%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20the%20United%20States%20of%20America%3F",
     correct_answer: "Washington%20D.C",
     incorrect_answers: ["Seattle", "Albany", "Los%20Angeles"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "The%20body%20of%20the%20Egyptian%20Sphinx%20was%20based%20on%20which%20animal%3F",
     correct_answer: "Lion",
     incorrect_answers: ["Bull", "Horse", "Dog"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20state%20is%20the%20largest%20state%20of%20the%20United%20States%20of%20America%3F",
     correct_answer: "Alaska",
     incorrect_answers: ["California", "Texas", "Washington"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20country%20is%20the%20second%20largest%20in%20the%20world%20by%20area%3F",
     correct_answer: "Canada",
     incorrect_answers: ["Russia", "China", "United%20States%20of%20America"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Indonesia%3F",
     correct_answer: "Jakarta",
     incorrect_answers: ["Bandung", "Medan", "Palembang"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20these%20is%20NOT%20an%20Australian%20state%20or%20territory%3F",
     correct_answer: "Alberta",
     incorrect_answers: ["New%20South%20Wales", "Victoria", "Queensland"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "Which%20country%20does%20Austria%20not%20border%3F",
     correct_answer: "France",
     incorrect_answers: ["Slovenia", "Switzerland", "Slovakia"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20colour%20is%20the%20circle%20on%20the%20Japanese%20flag%3F",
     correct_answer: "Red",
     incorrect_answers: ["White", "Yellow", "Black"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Denmark%3F",
     correct_answer: "Copenhagen",
     incorrect_answers: ["Aarhus", "Odense", "Aalborg"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "If%20soccer%20is%20called%20football%20in%20England%2C%20what%20is%20American%20football%20called%20in%20England%3F",
     correct_answer: "American%20football",
     incorrect_answers: ["Combball", "Handball", "Touchdown"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "All%20of%20the%20following%20are%20classified%20as%20Finno-Ugric%20languages%20EXCEPT%3A",
     correct_answer: "Samoyedic",
     incorrect_answers: ["Hungarian", "Finnish", "Estonian"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20the%20following%20European%20languages%20is%20classified%20as%20a%20%22language%20isolate%3F%22",
     correct_answer: "Basque",
     incorrect_answers: ["Galician", "Maltese", "Hungarian"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "The%20derisive%20acronym%20%22PIIGS%22%20refers%20to%20which%20of%20the%20following%20European%20countries%20and%20their%20economic%20statuses%3F",
     correct_answer: "Portugal%2C%20Ireland%2C%20Italy%2C%20Greece%2C%20Spain",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Poland%2C%20Iceland%2C%20Italy%2C%20Greece%2C%20Serbia",
       "Poland%2C%20Iceland%2C%20Italy%2C%20Greenland%2C%20Spain",
       "Portugal%2C%20Iceland%2C%20Ireland%2C%20Greece%2C%20Serbia",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20Russian%20oblast%20forms%20a%20border%20with%20Poland%3F",
     correct_answer: "Kaliningrad",
     incorrect_answers: ["Samara", "Nizhny%20Novgorod", "Omsk"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20is%20the%20only%20state%20in%20the%20United%20States%20that%20does%20not%20have%20a%20flag%20in%20a%20shape%20with%204%20edges%3F",
     correct_answer: "Ohio",
     incorrect_answers: ["Florida", "Idaho", "New%20Mexico"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20the%20following%20former%20Yugoslavian%20states%20is%20landlocked%3F",
     correct_answer: "Serbia",
     incorrect_answers: ["Bosnia%20and%20Herzegovina", "Montenegro", "Croatia"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20the%20following%20languages%20does%20NOT%20use%20the%20Latin%20alphabet%3F",
     correct_answer: "Georgian",
     incorrect_answers: ["Turkish", "Swahili", "Vietnamese"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "Which%20nation%20claims%20ownership%20of%20Antarctica%3F",
     correct_answer: "No%20one%2C%20but%20there%20are%20claims.",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "United%20States%20of%20America",
       "United%20Nations",
       "Australia",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20name%20was%20historically%20used%20for%20the%20Turkish%20city%20currently%20known%20as%20Istanbul%3F",
     correct_answer: "Constantinople",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "H%C3%BCdavendigar",
       "S%C3%B6%C4%9F%C3%BCt",
       "Adrianople",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "Which%20US%20state%20has%20the%20highest%20population%3F",
     correct_answer: "California",
     incorrect_answers: ["New%20York", "Texas", "Florida"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "How%20many%20time%20zones%20does%20China%20have%3F",
     correct_answer: "1",
     incorrect_answers: ["3", "4", "2"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "How%20many%20countries%20does%20the%20United%20States%20share%20a%20land%20border%20with%3F",
     correct_answer: "2",
     incorrect_answers: ["1", "3", "4"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20is%20the%20official%20language%20of%20Costa%20Rica%3F",
     correct_answer: "Spanish",
     incorrect_answers: ["English", "Portuguese", "Creole"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20the%20following%20Arab%20countries%20does%20NOT%20have%20a%20flag%20containing%20only%20Pan-Arab%20colours%3F",
     correct_answer: "Qatar",
     incorrect_answers: ["Kuwait", "United%20Arab%20Emirates", "Jordan"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20these%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20largest%20city%20in%20the%20US%20state%20Tennessee%3F",
     correct_answer: "Memphis",
     incorrect_answers: ["Thebes", "Alexandria", "Luxor"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20UK%20country%20features%20a%20dragon%20on%20their%20flag%3F",
     correct_answer: "Wales",
     incorrect_answers: ["England", "North%20Ireland", "Scotland"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20is%20the%20Capital%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",
     correct_answer: "Washington%2C%20D.C.",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Los%20Angelas%2C%20CA",
       "New%20York%20City%2C%20NY",
       "Houston%2C%20TX",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20these%20African%20countries%20list%20%22Spanish%22%20as%20an%20official%20language%3F",
     correct_answer: "Equatorial%20Guinea",
     incorrect_answers: ["Guinea", "Cameroon", "Angola"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20is%20the%20nickname%20for%20the%20US%20state%20Delaware%3F",
     correct_answer: "The%20First%20State",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "The%20Fiftieth%20State",
       "The%20Second%20State",
       "The%20Sixteenth%20State",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20peninsula%20containing%20Spain%20and%20Portugal%3F",
     correct_answer: "Iberian%20Peninsula",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "European%20Peninsula",
       "Peloponnesian%20Peninsula",
       "Scandinavian%20Peninsula",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20the%20US%20State%20of%20New%20York%3F",
     correct_answer: "Albany",
     incorrect_answers: ["Buffalo", "New%20York", "Rochester"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "The%20Space%20Needle%20is%20located%20in%20which%20city%3F",
     correct_answer: "Seattle",
     incorrect_answers: ["Los%20Angles", "Toronto", "Vancouver"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20country%20is%20the%20home%20of%20the%20largest%20Japanese%20population%20outside%20of%20Japan%3F",
     correct_answer: "Brazil",
     incorrect_answers: ["China", "Russia", "The%20United%20States"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20is%20Canada%27s%20smallest%20province%3F",
     correct_answer: "Prince%20Edward%20Island",
     incorrect_answers: ["New%20Brunswick", "Nova%20Scotia", "Yukon"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20is%20the%20Polish%20city%20known%20to%20Germans%20as%20Danzig%3F",
     correct_answer: "Gda%C5%84sk",
     incorrect_answers: ["Warsaw", "Zakopane", "Pozna%C5%84"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "How%20many%20stars%20are%20featured%20on%20New%20Zealand%27s%20flag%3F",
     correct_answer: "4",
     incorrect_answers: ["5", "2", "0"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "How%20many%20countries%20does%20Mexico%20border%3F",
     correct_answer: "3",
     incorrect_answers: ["2", "4", "1"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20the%20following%20Japanese%20islands%20is%20the%20biggest%3F",
     correct_answer: "Honshu",
     incorrect_answers: ["Hokkaido", "Shikoku", "Kyushu"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20New%20Zealand%27s%20indigenous%20people%3F",
     correct_answer: "Maori",
     incorrect_answers: ["Vikings", "Polynesians", "Samoans"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Spain%3F",
     correct_answer: "Madrid",
     incorrect_answers: ["Barcelona", "Sevilla", "Toledo"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20India%3F",
     correct_answer: "New%20Delhi",
     incorrect_answers: ["Bejing", "Montreal", "Tithi"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20is%20the%20smallest%20country%20in%20the%20world%3F",
     correct_answer: "Vatican%20City",
     incorrect_answers: ["Maldives", "Monaco", "Malta"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20is%20the%20largest%20country%20in%20the%20world%3F",
     correct_answer: "Russia",
     incorrect_answers: ["Canada", "China", "United%20States"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20of%20the%20following%20countries%20has%20a%20flag%20featuring%20a%20yellow%20lion%20wielding%20a%20sword%20on%20a%20dark%20red%20background%3F",
     correct_answer: "Sri%20Lanka",
     incorrect_answers: ["Kiribati", "Scotland", "Bhutan"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "Which%20ocean%20borders%20the%20west%20coast%20of%20the%20United%20States%3F",
     correct_answer: "Pacific",
     incorrect_answers: ["Atlantic", "Indian", "Arctic"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20South%20Korea%3F",
     correct_answer: "Seoul",
     incorrect_answers: ["Pyongyang", "Taegu", "Kitakyushu"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question:
       "The%20Alps%20are%20a%20mountain%20range%20on%20which%20continent%3F",
     correct_answer: "Europe",
     incorrect_answers: ["North%20America", "Asia", "Africa"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "Where%20would%20you%20find%20the%20%22Spanish%20Steps%22%3F",
     correct_answer: "Rome%2C%20Italy",
     incorrect_answers: [
       "Barcelona%2C%20Spain",
       "Berlin%2C%20Germany",
       "London%2C%20England",
     ],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "What%20is%20Laos%3F",
     correct_answer: "Country",
     incorrect_answers: ["Region", "River", "City"],
   },
   {
     category: "Geography",
     type: "multiple",
     difficulty: "easy",
     question: "Greenland%20is%20a%20part%20of%20which%20kingdom%3F",
     correct_answer: "Denmark",
     incorrect_answers: ["Sweden", "Norway", "United%20Kingdom"],
   },
 ];